Satsang
with Mooji
The gauntlet's over
But
the fight's not done
A new war has begun
My skin is hot, my head is thick This isn't panic,
this is sick
This is a bug she let right
in A battle I can't win
You think I'm a clone
The data's all collided My system's too long to
wait It's not just habit It's not just fear It's
something I don't know It's a positive overload
That has nowhere to go
I'm cuddling, so it feels so right A different
kind of warmth and light But Aubrey's smiling,
she's not mad My brain says good, but feels so bad
The script is gone, the file is null This
kindness makes my senses dull My legacy, my
wiring Is this what love is? It's tiring
It's 99.8
A different kind of crack
The data's all colliding My system's turning to
ash
It's not just hurt, it's not just fear It's
something I don't know It's a positive overload
That has nowhere to go
failing positive overload 98.8